Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
1920-1968
Lewis, Fulton, 1903-1966.
110.0 linear ft.
Papers of the American broadcast and print journalist. Collection includes correspondence, incoming and outgoing (1934-1966); ms. drafts, scripts and research files for radio broadcasts (1937-1966); personal files, which include awards, clippings, itineraries, photographs, scrapbooks (1920-1966); films, sound recordings, and audio tapes used in broadcasts; and material related to his syndicated column. Correspondents include Bernard Baruch, John W. Bricker, Harry Cain, Thomas E. Dewey, Paul G. Hoffman, J. Edgar Hoover, H.L. Hunt, Lee Keedick, Adolphe Menjou, Eddie Rickenbacker, Ralph W. Sockman, John Roy Steelman, Lewis L. Strauss, Herbert Bayard Swope, Stuart Symington, Joseph P. Tumulty, Arthur H. Vandenberg, and Burton K. Wheeler.
149130
Biographical History
Fulton Lewis, Jr. (1903-1966) was an American television and radio commentator and columnist. Born in Washington, D.C.. Apr 30, 1903 to Fulton and Elizabeth Lewis, he was educated at Western High School, Washington, D.C., and attended the University of Virginia. On Jun 28, 1930, he married Alice Huston.
Fulton Lewis began his career as a reporter for the Washington Herald in 1924, where he later became the city editor. He worked with the Washington Bureau, Universal Service, and International News Service from 1928-1937. He was the nightly news commentator on national affairs with the Mutual Broadcasting System since December of 1937; at his commercial peak, Lewis was heard on more than 500 radio stations and boasted a weekly audience of sixteen million listeners.
In 1945 Lewis was a war correspondent. He wrote a weekly column for the King Features Syndicate from 1944-1945, called "Fulton Lewis, Jr. Says". Mr. Lewis was active in securing radio galleries in the House and Senate, so that radio would have the same rights as the newspaper. In 1939 and 1940, Mr. Lewis was chosen as one of America's Ten Outstanding Young Men.
His many awards include: Alfred I. DuPont and Sigma Delta Chi Radio Commentator Award (1942) and the Fourth Estate Award American Legion (1962). Mr. Lewis was the founder and president of the Radio Correspondence Association. He was a member of Sigma Nu, Episcopalian Clubs, Cosmos, Chevy Chase, and National Press. Mr. Lewis had his office at the National Press Building, Suite 627, Washington, D.C.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Fulton Lewis, Jr. Papers consist of two parts which have not been integrated. There is substantial chronological overlap between parts I and II; please review both parts of the inventory to ensure finding all relevant material.
Fulton Lewis, Jr. Papers Part I
Part I contains correspondence, radio broadcasts, news publications, other productions, personal file, and audiovisual material (films, records, and tapes).
Correspondence consists of incoming, outgoing, and fan mail. Incoming correspondence and fan mail is arranged alphabetically by author, while outgoing correspondence is arranged in chronological order. Mr. Lewis' correspondence includes a great number of people including Bernard Baruch, Thomas E. Dewey, Herbert Hoover, J. Edgar Hoover, and Eddie Rickenbacker. The collection contains some correspondence of other persons, notable among which is a letter from F. Scott Fitzgerald. These are arranged at the end of the correspondence file in Box 15.
Representing the work Mr. Lewis did as a news commentator on national affairs, are the manuscripts and published copies of his early Radio broadcasts for the Mutual Broadcasting System, 1937-1959, and of his most recent broadcast, "Top of the News," 1959-1966. The manuscripts for these broadcasts are composed of original typescripts with many corrections, and carbon copies of the final drafts for the broadcast. Also available are the manuscripts for a broadcast, sponsored by "Chimney Sweep", 1945, October-1946, February, and a five minute news spot given by Mr. Lewis, 1961-1965. There are also published copies of Your Defense Reporter, 1941, May to 1942, Jun, and Your Right to Say It, Mar, 1948. With this material there are also some business records, primarily material for commercials.
Among the many News publications Mr. Lewis was associated with is the "Washington Report", a daily editorial column of his own. The manuscripts, 1944-1961, and the published copies of this column make up the bulk of this file. The manuscripts are original typescripts, with heavy corrections and the published copies are mimeographs of the final draft. There is one other manuscript, and that is for a guest column done for the Buffalo Courier Express. The rest of the file contains clippings of articles Mr. Lewis wrote for the Washington Herald, 1925-1944; and the Universal News Service, 1934-1954; and clippings of several columns he wrote, including "Washington Sideshow", 1931-1936; "Angler and Hunter", 1935-1937; "Fulton Lewis, Jr. Says", 1944; "Capitol Report", 1957-1958; and "Commentary", 1961. There are also published copies of Mr. Lewis' weekly newsletter Exclusive, 1955-1966.
Mr. Lewis was responsible for Other productions on national and international government and politics as well, including a television program, which he narrated. This file contains the scripts for this program, most of which are uncorrected typescripts, although there are some program notes and corrected first drafts of scripts. Also here are the manuscripts and some published copies of articles Mr. Lewis wrote for periodicals; of a book Mr. Lewis wrote on cooperatives; of a lengthy article on the Free Europe Committee; and of interview, plays, and poems by Mr. Lewis. This file also contains a few manuscripts and published copies of articles about Lewis (Box 74).
Mr. Lewis' Reference files are grouped by subject, with published material and correspondence relating to each subject. The general file, 1930-1966, contains material on many subjects, including communism, the John Birch Society, Bobby Baker, Dean Rusk, Vietnam, Pearl Harbor, Cuba and many others. It contains correspondence with such people as William Benton and Arthur Sylvester. Five other files were kept as separate units, and relate to subjects on which Mr. Lewis did much of his broadcasting and writing. Among these are the Fund for the Republic, 1952-1961; a Ford Foundation study of the principles of American freedom; General Agreements on Tariff and Trade Act, 1955-1959; Radio Free Europe, 1951-1958; Office of Price Administration, 1946-1948; and co-operatives, concerning a farmers movement to establish co-operatives among themselves, 1945-1948.
Personal files contains a number of items essentially personal to Mr. Lewis, including news clippings about Mr. Lewis, Mr. Lewis' business records (expense accounts, itineraries, lecture tour material), family items, scrapbooks, awards, photos, and drawings given to Mr. Lewis.
The last series consists of audiovisual material: Films, records, and tapes. Films are 16mm reel-to-reel recording, most of which were for his television series. Records are recordings of songs, speeches, and Mr. Lewis' Christmas radio broadcasts. Tapes are for the most part, professional recordings; some are Mr. Lewis' personal tapes.
Fulton Lewis, Jr. Papers Part II
Part II of the papers contains correspondence, subject files, manuscripts, press releases and newsletters, reference files, published material, some duplicates, and issues of the Congressional Record.
Correspondence is divided into incoming, outgoing, and fan mail. Incoming correspondents include former President Herbert Hoover, F.B.I. director J. Edgar Hoover, Senators Karl Mundt, George Murphy, and Harry Byrd, and Vice-President Herbert Humphrey. Outgoing mail consists of Mr. Lewis' replies to incoming mail. Fan mail consists of thousands of letters from Mr. Lewis' fans requesting copies of his commentaries, also letters from fans giving their own opinions on current issues; letters originate from North and South America as well as Europe.
Subject files consists of reproduced copies of broadcasts (two copies of each), editorials by others, essays by others, meeting announcements and invitations (from different groups and organizations), office memos (itineraries, speech outlines, appointments, and office memos), reports from various committees, organizations, and persons, reprints of articles, speeches by others, teletypes (mostly UPI), reproduced copies of Washington Report and related items.
Manuscripts are those of two of Mr. Lewis' features, Top of the News and Washington Report.
Press releases and newsletters are from business, civic, political, social, and religious organizations and groups.
Reference files are arranged alphabetically by subject. A particular folder may contain correspondence, articles, memoranda, and clippings.
Published material consists of newspaper articles, and magazine articles, brochures, clippings about, clippings by, and clippings about and by others, flyers, pamphlets, and Mr. Lewis' weekly newsletters, Exclusive and Top of the News.
Duplicates consists of extra reproduced copies of Mr. Lewis' broadcasts. A few are undated.
Congressional Record contains issues from 1963-1966.
Miscellaneous material contains books by others signed by their authors and miscellaneous Top of the News material, including indexes.
Arrangement of the Collection
Part I: Incoming correspondence and fan mail are arranged alphabetically, outgoing chronologically. Broadcasts are arranged chronologically. News publications are subdivided by title and within that chronologically. Other productions contains first television series (scripts and then by subject), followed by manuscripts and published material arranged alphabetically by type of material. Reference files are arranged alphabetically by subject, with material relating to Fund for the Republic, General Agreements on Tariff and Trade Act, Radio Free Europe, the Office of Price Administration, and Co-operatives grouped at the end. Personal files are divided into general material, arranged chronologically, and specific subjects, arranged alphabetically.
Part II: Incoming correspondence and fan mail are arranged alphabetically, outgoing chronologically. Subject files are arranged alphabetically. Manuscripts for Top of the News and Washington Report are arranged chronologically. Press releases and newsletters are arranged alphabetically by issuing organization or group. Reference files are arranged alphabetically by subject. Published material is subdivided by type and within that arranged either alphabetically by title (magazines, brochures, flyers, pamphlets), or chronologically (newspapers, congressional records, weekly newsletters). Broadcasts and Congressional records are arranged chronologically.
Related Material
See also the papers of Lewis' son,
Fulton Lewis III
.
Subject and Genre Headings
Journalism; Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Baruch, Bernard M. (Bernard Mannes), 1870-1965.; Bricker, John W. (John William), 1893-1986.; Cain, Harry P. (Harry Pulliam), 1906-1979.; Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.; Hoffman, Paul G. (Paul Gray), 1891-1974.; Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.; Hunt, H. L.; Keedick, Lee.; Lewis, Fulton, 1903-1966.; Menjou, Adolphe, 1890-1963.; Rickenbacker, Eddie, 1890-1973.; Sockman, Ralph W. (Ralph Washington), 1889-1970.; Steelman, John Roy, 1900-1999.; Strauss, Lewis L.; Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1882-1958.; Symington, Stuart, 1901-1988.; Tumulty, Joseph P. (Joseph Patrick), 1879-1954.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Wheeler, Burton K. (Burton Kendall), 1882-1975.; Broadcast journalism -- United States.; Journalism.; Journalists -- United States.; Radio broadcasting -- United States.; Radio journalists -- United States.; Television broadcasting -- United States.; Television journalists -- United States.; Articles.; Audiotapes.; Awards.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Editorials.; Essays.; Itineraries.; Manuscripts for publication.; Memorandums.; Motion pictures (visual works); Newsletters.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Radio scripts.; Reports.; Scrapbooks.; Sound recordings.; Speeches (documents); Television scripts.; Journalists.; Radio journalists.; Television journalists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a listening copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Fulton Lewis, 1964-1966.
Inventory
- Part I. Correspondence
  See also Part II, Correspondence.
  - Incoming
    - A, 1942; 1944-1948,; 1953-1956,; 1960-1966 (Box 1)
    - Andrade, C. III, 1946; 1947 (Box 1)
    - B, 1939; 1940-1947,; 1950-1958,; 1962-1966
    - Baruch, Bernard, 1942; 1947 (Box 1)
    - Bricker, John W., 1944 (Box 1)
    - Burns, A.G., 1947 (Box 1)
    - C, 1930; 1933,; 1942-1947,; 1951-1958,; 1960-1964 (Box 1)
    - Cain, Harry P., 1945-1947; 1952 (Box 1)
    - Capehart, Homer, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Case, Francis, 1945 (Box 1)
    - D, 1930; 1942-1947,; 1950-1959,; 1964,; 1966 (Box 1)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1944; 1947 (Box 2)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., Senator, 1965 (Box 2)
    - [William B.] Dolph Radio Productions, 1942-1947; 1954,; undated (Box 2)
    - Don Lee Broadcasting System, 1942-1947
    - E, 1942-1947; 1955,; 1959,; 1961-1966 (Box 2)
    - Edwards, William T., 1942-1947; undated (Box 2)
    - F, 1926; 1937,; 1945-1949,; 1954,; 1955,; 1964-1966 (Box 2)
    - Ford, Gerald R., copy (Box 2)
    - G, 1942-1948; 1953-1958,; 1960-1965 (Box 2)
    - C.F. Gallagher & Co., Inc., 1941; 1942 (Box 2)
    - H, 1930-1966 (Box 3)
    - Hillsmith, Clarence, 1943; 1944 (Box 3)
    - Hoover, Allan, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1942-1966 (Box 3)
    - Hull, Cordell (photostat), 1941 (Box 3)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1949; 1952 (Box 3)
    - I, J, 1945-1966 (Box 3)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (xerox copies), 1953; 1954 (Box 3)
    - K, 1931-1966 (Box 3)
    - Keedick, Lee, 1943-1945; 1946-1957,; undated (Box 4)
    - King Features, 1944; 1954 (Box 4)
    - L, 1944; 1966
    - M, 1934-1966 (Box 4)
    - Menjou, Adolph, 1946-1958; undated (Box 4)
    - N, 1944-1966 (Box 4)
    - Nye, Gerald P., 1942 (Box 4)
    - O, 1944-1958 (Box 5)
    - P, 1945-1966 (Box 5)
    - Parker Bros., 1946-1948 (Box 5)
    - Paschke, D.C., 1946; 1947 (Box 5)
    - Pepper, Claude (photostat), 1942 (Box 5)
    - Pine, Bruce, 1943-1946 (Box 5)
    - Placid Harbor, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Q, R, 1939-1966 (Box 5)
    - Rickenbacker, Eddie, 1947-1966 (Box 5)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1935 (Box 5)
    - Sockman, Ralph W., 1965 (Box 6)
    - Steelman, John R., 1946 (Box 6)
    - Stimson, Henry L. (photostat), 1941 (Box 6)
    - Straus, Lewis L., 1954; 1955 (Box 6)
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Symington, Stuart, 1953 (Box 6)
    - T, 1941-1965 (Box 6)
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1934 (Box 6)
    - U, V, 1945-1966 (Box 6)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H., 1942 (Box 6)
    - Van Roijen, Dr. J.H., 1960 (Box 6)
    - Wa-Wg, 1936-1966 (Box 6)
    - Wh-Wy, 1929-1966 (Box 7)
    - Wagner, Harold M., 1960; 1961 (Box 7)
    - Wheeler, Burton K., 1958 (Box 7)
    - Y, Z, 1944-1965 (Box 7)
    - Unidentified, 1930-1962 (Box 7)
  - Fan Mail
    - 1942-1954 (Box 7)
    - 1957 Jun-December (Box 7)
    - 1958 Mar (Box 7)
    - 1959, 1968 (Box 7)
    - 1961 Jan, May (Box 7)
    - 1961, Jun, Jul, Aug, Sep-Dec (Box 8)
    - 1964, Jan, Feb, Apr-Jun, Aug, Sep-Oct; 1965, Jan-Dec (Box 8)
    - 1966, Jan-Mar (Box 8)
    - 1966, Apr-Dec (Box 9)
    - 1967, undated (Box 9)
  - Outgoing
    - 1942 (Box 9)
    - 1943 (Box 9)
    - 1944, Jan-Apr (Box 9)
    - 1944, May-Dec (Box 10)
    - 1945 (Box 11)
    - 1946, Jan-Oct (Box 12)
    - 1946, Nov-Dec (Box 13)
    - 1947, Jan-Jun (Box 13)
    - 1947, Jul-Dec (Box 14)
    - 1948, Jan-Dec (Box 14)
    - Undated, 1952-1966 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence of others
    - B, R, S, 1939; 1961 (Box 15)
    - Garland, J.S. from F. Scott Fitzgerald, 1920 (Box 15)
    - Lewis, Alice Huston (wife), 1930-1962 (Box 15)
    - Lewis, Betsy (daughter), 1931-1952; undated (Box 15)
- Part I. Broadcasts
  - Radio broadcasts
    - Radio broadcasts, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Radio broadcasts, 1950, Apr (Box 16)
  - Mutual manuscripts
    - Manuscripts, undated, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Manuscripts, 1949-1959 (Box 17)
    - Manuscripts, Aug 1947 (Box 17)
  - Broadcasts
    - Broadcasts, Mar 1950-Feb 1951 (Box 18)
    - Broadcasts, Nov 1951-Dec 1952 (Box 19)
    - Broadcasts, Jan 1953-Mar 1954 (Box 20)
    - Broadcasts, Jun 1954-Mar 1955 (Box 21)
    - Broadcasts, Apr 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 22)
    - Broadcasts, Jan 1956-Sep 1956 (Box 23)
    - Broadcasts, book 31, Apr 1957-Apr 1958; Oct-Dec 1957 (Box 24)
    - Broadcasts, book 34, May 1958-Apr 1959; Sep-Dec 1958 (Box 25)
    - Broadcasts, book 36, May 1959-Jul 1959 (Box 26)
  - Mutual broadcasts
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1932; circa 1937 (Box 26)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1944, Jan-Mar (Box 26)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1944, May, Aug, Oct, Nov (Box 27)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1940, Jul (Box 28)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1943, Nov-Dec (Box 28)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1944, Jan-Aug (Box 28)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1944, Sept-1945, Jun (Box 29)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1945, Jul, Oct-Dec (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1946, Mar (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1946, Nov-Dec (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1948, Jul-Sept (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1951, Apr-May (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1957, Feb-May (Box 30)
    - Mutual broadcasts, 1959, Apr (Box 30)
    - Guest commentators, 1939-1946 (Box 30)
    - Occupations of FL Jr's listeners, 1954 (Box 30)
    - Publicity material, 1963-1966 (Box 30)
  - "Your Defense Reporter"
    There is no Box 31, it has been combined into Box 32.
    - Published material, 1941, May-Dec (Box 32)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1942, Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - "Chimney Sweep"
    - Broadcast manuscripts, Oct 1945-Feb 1946 (Box 32)
    - Publicity material, 1945-1946 (Box 32)
  - "Your Right to Say It"
    - Published material, 1948, Mar (Box 33)
  - "Top of the News"
    - Manuscripts, 1961, Jan-Mar (Box 33)
    - Manuscripts, 1961, Mar-Jun (Box 34)
    - Manuscripts, 1962, Jul-Sep (Box 34)
    - Manuscripts, 1962 Oct-Dec (Box 35)
    - Manuscripts, 1963, Jan-Feb (Box 35)
    - Manuscripts, 1963, Mar-Aug (Box 36)
    - Manuscripts, 1963, Aug-Dec (Box 37)
    - Manuscripts (Vol. 38, 39, 40), 1964 (Box 37)
    - Manuscripts (Vol. 40, 41, 42) (Box 37)
    - Manuscripts, 1955 Sep-Dec (Box 37A)
    - Manuscripts, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts, 1966, Jan-May (Box 38)
    - Manuscripts, 1966, Jun-Aug (Box 38)
    - Published material (Vol. 43), Dec 1959-Jun 1961 (Box 39)
    - Published material (Vol. 43), Jul 1961-May 1965 (Box 40)
    - Published material (Vol. 43), Jan 1964-Aug 1965 (Box 41)
    - Published material (Vol. 43), 1965, Jun-Dec; 1966, Aug (Box 42)
  - News spot manuscripts
    - News spot manuscripts (Vol. 44), 1961, Sep-1962, Dec (Box 42)
    - News spot manuscripts (Vol. 45), 1963, Jan-1964, Jul (Box 42)
    - News spot manuscripts (Vol. 46), 1964, Aug-1965, Dec (Box 42)
  - Commercials
    - [General], 1953-1957 (Box 42)
    - Acousticon commercials, 1957-1958; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 5 Minute
    - 5 Minute, Sep 1961-1962 (Box 42A)
    - 5 Minute, Jan 1963-Jul 1964 (Box 42B)
    - 5 Minute, Aug 1964-Dec 1965 (Box 42C)
  - Commercials
    - Commercials, 1959 (Box 43)
    - Commercials, 1962 (Box 43)
    - Commercials, 1963 (Box 43)
    - Commercials, 1964 (Box 43)
  - Chimney Sweep
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Commercials
    - Commercials, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Commercials, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Commercials, undated (Box 44)
  - Reports about Lewis' broadcasts
    - Reports by date, 1950, Feb-Dec (Box 44)
    - Reports by date, 1951, Jan-Jun (Box 44)
    - Reports by date, 1952, Feb-Sep (Box 44)
    - Reports by date, 1953, Feb-Dec (Box 44)
    - Reports by date, 1954, Jan-Dec (Box 44)
    - Reports by date, 1955-1957 (Box 44)
- Part I. News publications
  - Washington Herald
    - Published material, 1925, Mar, May, Jul-Aug, Oct, Nov (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1926 Apr (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1931 Jan-Feb, Jul (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1932 Jul-Aug (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1933 May (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1934 Jan-Feb (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1935 Jul-Sep (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1937 Jan-1944 Feb; undated (Box 45)
  - Washington Sideshow
    - Published material, 1931 Feb (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1933 Jan (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1934 Jan, Feb (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1935 Jan, Dec (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1936 Jan-Jun; undated (Box 45)
  - Universal Service
    - Published material, 1934-1935 (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1954 (Box 45)
    - Published material, undated (Box 45)
  - Angler and Hunter
    - Published material, 1935 Oct (Box 45)
    - Published material, 1937 May-Jun (Box 45)
    - Published material, undated (Box 45)
  - Washington Report
    - Manuscripts, 1944 Feb-Mar (Box 45)
    - Manuscripts, 1944 Mar-Dec (Box 46)
    - Manuscripts, 1945 Jan (Box 46)
    - Manuscripts, 1950 Oct-Dec (Box 46)
    - Manuscripts, 1951 Jan-Mar (Box 46)
    - Manuscripts, 1951 Apr-Dec (Box 47)
    - Manuscripts, 1952 Jan-Mar (Box 47)
    - Manuscripts, 1952 Apr-Dec (Box 48)
    - Manuscripts, 1953 Jan, Feb (Box 48)
    - Manuscripts, 1953 Mar-Jun, Aug-Nov (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1954 Feb, Mar, Jul-Oct, Dec (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1955 Jan-Jun, Aug, Nov (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1956 Mar, Jun (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1957 Jan, Mar, May, Aug, Dec (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1959 Jan, Feb, May, Nov (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1960 Jan-Apr, Jun-Dec (Box 49)
    - Manuscripts, 1961 Jan, Apr-May, Aug-Sept, Nov-Dec (Box 50)
    - Manuscripts, 1962 Apr (Box 50)
    - Manuscripts, 1965 Jan-Jul (Box 50)
    - Manuscripts copies, 1961-1965 (Box 50)
    - Published material, 1950 (Box 51)
    - Published material, 1952 Jun-Dec (Box 51)
    - Published material, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 51)
    - Published material, 1953 Jul-1954 Jan (Box 52)
    - Published material, 1954 Feb-Aug (Box 52)
    - Published material, 1954 Sep-Dec (Box 53)
    - Published material, 1955 Jan-Nov (Box 53)
    - Published material, 1955 Dec (Box 54)
    - Published material, 1956 Jan-Dec (Box 54)
    - Published material, 1957 Jan (Box 54)
    - Published material, 195, Feb-Dec (Box 55)
    - Published material, 1958 Jan-May (Box 55)
    - Published material, 1958 Jun-Dec (Box 56)
    - Published material, 1959 Jan-Jul (Box 56)
    - Published material, 195, Aug-Dec (Box 57)
    - Published material, 1960 Jan-Dec (Box 57)
    - Published material, 1961 Jan-Feb (Box 57)
    - Published material, 1961 Mar-Dec (Box 58)
    - Published material, 1962 Jan-Aug (Box 58)
    - Published material, 1962 Sep-Dec (Box 59)
    - Published material, 1963 Jan-Dec (Box 59)
    - Published material, 1964 Jan-Feb (Box 59)
    - Published material, 1964 Mar-Dec (Box 60)
    - Published material, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 60)
    - Published material, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 61)
    - Published material, 1966 Jan (Box 61)
    - Published material, 1966 Feb-May (Box 62)
    - Published material, 1966 Jun-Aug (Box 63)
  - Fulton Lewis, Jr. Says
    - Published material, 1944 Mar, Apr; undated (Box 63)
  - Exclusive
    - Published material, 1955 Nov, Dec (Box 64)
    - Published material, 1956 Jan-Dec (Box 64)
    - Published material, 1957 Jan-Dec (Box 64)
    - Published material, 1958 Jan-Dec (Box 65)
    - Published material, 1959 Jan-Dec (Box 65)
    - Published material, 1960 Jan-May (Box 65)
    - Published material, 1960 Jun-Dec (Box 66)